ED.
Q. What did you do?
We went back to the hotel.
And afterwards, I was feeling a little hungry,
I went for a walk.
And then I saw a corner restaurant.
It was crowded at the corner, so I thought, "What should I do?
So I went for a walk and found a sushi restaurant.
And I found a sushi restaurant where I could eat for 2,000 yen.
So I decided to go in.
And when I entered, I became friends with everyone.
I became friends with everyone.
I was surprised.
I was surprised at myself.
Was it good?
It was so delicious,
I made friends with everyone.
That's what I'm talking about.
You surprised me.
How is that possible? I thought, "That's not possible.
I thought I might be a genius.
At that moment, I was convinced that I could survive anywhere.
Next microphone. Please.
Hey, hey, hey, ha, ha.
Want to give it a shot?
Look at the unexpected one.
Something a little more in the shape of a circle.
Yes, please.
Chucy is fine today.
I was charging my headphones yesterday, but I forgot both the charger and the headphones,
I bought the charger because it was a type C charger that also charges my cell phone, so I couldn't charge it.
Here is what I bought at Date.
Type C quick charger.
I was shocked.
Delicious. I put a little ponzu (Japanese citrus juice) in it to give it a sour taste.
It tastes really good.
They say it makes them very nervous.
They can't stop laughing.
I'm so nervous that I can't stop laughing.
The corners of his mouth are down.
It's fun, isn't it?
Calm down.
We'll live together.
Think about it, senior.
How'd it go with my chi?
We'll keep talking about it.
It's nice to be able to say that to each other and build each other up.
I can tell by the taste of your love.
I'm here at Iwate Park.
I came to Iwate Park.
It's something, you know, when I finished and I noticed, you know, look.
There's a lot of candy pins on here.
I wonder what they are.
I ate them.
It's delicious.
White Kutcher
Separate photo work